Yes, salmon roe is good too, but the sujiko is better, because you feel like you're eating an egg.
It's like you're eating an egg.
The salmon too!
I'll tell you, it's a picture of Mariko.
That's right! Don't make fun of me!
It was like I had a vision.
You can't find this at the supermarket.
They don't sell it.
About a third, right?
Almost.
Well, even half of this is big.
It's like, "Wow!
I love it. It's like New Year's.
It's like New Year's, isn't it?
I wonder if it's got oil on it.
I know, right?
It's so bright, so bright, so bright, so smartly, so smartly, so smartly, so smartly
Match, match, match, match!
Match is such a loud voice.
I don't think it's the same at all. I'm starting to think that I shouldn't even try to imitate him anymore.
It's better if I don't do it. Like, I can just say the lines.
I feel a little bad for Machi, so I'm just telling him to mind his own business.
I can't wait for New Year's. We can splurge a little.
Salmon roe, salmon roe... and herring roe...
You know, dried herring roe.
It's in the osechi-chi.
The king of crunchy foods.
Osechi...
You know, those crunchy, salty things.
Datemaki eggs and beans...
It's sweet.
It's like a catch-all between sweet and sour.
I never get tired of the communication.
It's good.
It's so New Year's.
I like it. I really do.
Well, well, well.
And the other thing...
Midori-ku, Yokohama.
Mr. Green Clown!
Thank you.
I was on a trip the other day.
I took the limited express Kuroshio from Shin-Osaka to Wakayama!
Wakayama has a famous zoo, right in Shirahama where there are lots of pandas, so the express train has a wonderful appearance.
May I?
Cute pandas!
Pandas!
This one is called Kuroshio.
I thought he'd be a little blacker.
It's cute.
Maybe it's a reference to that zoo over there.
There are a lot of pandas in the zoo.
I see.
There are a lot of pandas there.
Adventure World
I didn't know it had such a Western-style name.
It sounds like a theme park.
But it is famous for what Shirahama is, isn't it?
Shirahama Town
But it says "Adventure World" in the comments.
It's Adventure World, isn't it?
If you look closely, the panda is a little angry.
It's true.
He's a little cranky.
They don't even feed him.
You make him run.
Give me some feed. Give me some feed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, well, well, well...
That's how it is, sir.
Well, then...
Well...
I'll go to this corner.
I'm going to go to this corner.
So...
Well... it's the last creature creation of the year, isn't it?
That's right.
We're going to finish the creation of living things.
That's great.
Wait a minute.
I'm thinking of doing a search.
Please.
Perch, please.
Wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
What's up?
How's it coming?
Wait a minute.
Let's see, here's what I found.
Yes.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Go on.
Come on!
Come on.
It's not stuck.
Wait a minute.
It won't catch.
Please deliver Pulponte!
There he is!
One moment, please.
I'll be with you in a moment.
There you are, from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, Master Sarpong Ebichu staff.
Good evening to the performers of the performers plus the staff. Good evening. It's so radio friendly.
It sure is.
That's how radio used to be.
Like "Good evening to the staff" on a postcard.
Everyone would ooh and aah over it.
That's right.
It brings back memories, doesn't it?
I emailed you to contribute to the Creative Creativity section.
Thank you very much.
May I have the creature's name?
Yes.
Nodoguro Mitsuoshie.
Nodoguro?
Nodoguro Mitsosier.
Nodoguro Mitsuoshie.
What?
I don't know.
This fish is almost like the answer.
Almost like an answer.
Fish.
Hey.
Three black throats.
There's one, right?
Black throats?
Yes.
In Kanazawa?
That's right.
The doomed ones.
Super-premium fish.
High-end fish.
Super Fine Fish
Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine Superfine
Either
Super Fine Fish
Super-premium fish
Nodoguro Triple Moe
Is it a fish?
I don't know.
Well, sister, it was written by me.
Nodoguro Mitsuoshie.
It doesn't come up at all.
But it's true, as you said before...
If you look at the answer, it's exactly the same.
Just like that.
It's not an esoteric name like usual.
It's no exaggeration to say that the creature's habits are all there.
What?
It's no exaggeration to say that it's all there.
I want to eat black throat!
I want to eat throat black!
Isn't there a lot of seafood this week?
That's right!
It's seafood week, right?
It's seafood week!
Throat black is in season, even for you.
It's a cold-weather fish.
Yellowtail... yellowtail...
Yellowtail.
I like yellowtail.
Nodoguro Mitsuoshie
Pacific bluefin tuna (Thunnus orientalis)
Mitsuoshie
Yes, yes, yes, yes
So so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so
So let's get it out... so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so
Yes, it doesn't come out at all
Great - maybe now it's an imitation of IKKO
like a nodagurah!
Like Nodagurah, like Nodagurah, like Nadagurah.
I don't care, but...
IKKO, you know...
You see her on TV a lot, don't you?
She cheers me up, doesn't she?
Yes, it does.
I wonder why.
It makes me want to give it my all.
I wish I could meet him.
I wish Deville would come.
I'd love to see you... please play a song.
I've seen it many times... but she made a calendar the other day...
Oh, right... new cosmetics...
Oh, right...
For me...
Nice!
Or a store where you buy things...
Purchase-like
throat black three presses
Mariko completed
Yes, sir.
Let's go to the front first, shall we?
Nodoguro mitsubushi hehe no way, I'll just return it with my eyes.
It's so cartoonish. Is it a world fish?
I've got a fish in my throat... but that's all right... where are the three pushes?
Where in here?
Mitsuoshie?
Mitsuoshie? Mitsuoshie?
I thought that wasn't included.
Nodoguro.
This is Nodoguro.
Nodoguro Mitsuoshie. Shall we go to the teacher then?
Yes. I'm here. Nodoguro Mitsuoshie.
Oh, indeed.
It looks like you're looking at it from above.
Yes, you are looking at it from around here.
Like this, when there are fish like this, you are looking at them like this.
That's right.
He has a black throat.
He tells me three things.
Gyo...
For example, ask him what's on your mind.
Then you'll tell me what I don't know?
Yes, just three things.
It's like the genie in the lamp.
He grants you three wishes.
Then, how do you operate a cell phone?
You say, "I don't understand this," like this.
Gyo...
I don't get it, Gyo-chan.
Is that a story? Is that what this is about?
It's pointless.
You didn't tell me three things.
You didn't tell me three things about the throat.
Yes, sir.
But you said you'd tell us now.
As a matter of fact, yes.
What?
Well, I'm afraid it's not a fish.
It's not a fish.
It's a bird.
It's a bird. It's called a honeyguide.
It tells humans where the honeycomb nests.
Such an effective bird!
Birds get nectar from the nest in the honey pot.
To get something useful for themselves.
Well, they can't take it if, say, a bee attacks them.
They use humans to guide us.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch.
They think, "Come here!
And then the humans do the same for them, and they get a share of the profits.
That's smart.
Amazing, isn't it?
That's great.
And there's a hive over here, and they're stepping in the shadows, too.
Just a hive.
It's hip-hop.
You grew up on hip-hop.
They're mostly friends. It's hip-hop! Oh, my God! I grew up on hip-hop.
We're mostly friends.
Friends, friends, friends.
Mostly friends.
You know, crows are smart, too.
They're very smart.
Birds are.
Wow! I didn't know there were birds like that.
Well, well, well. That was close.
Nice try!
You meant to tell me three things.
I'll just say it again, and you'll get a line back, so I'll just reflect on Mariko's too.
The world is the world.
Maybe they'll have an "o" festival in the museum.
Maybe they'll come.
You're all going to win!
Amazing.
He's got no will to live, does he?
This fish...
"I'm going to live from now on.
It's like...
It's like a bruise.
Hang in there.
What were you born for?
That's right, for what purpose were you born?
Well, well, well, well...
We'll continue with the creation of the creatures... even though it's the last one for this year.
We'll start again at the beginning of the new year.
If you have any ideas for creatures, please feel free to send them to us.
So, as you can see...
We are now broadcasting live.
First of all, I'd like to start off by saying a few words.
First of all, I'd like to make an announcement.
I'd like to inform you again.
Yes.
So...
We'll be having the Devil Festival in the museum again.
We'll have a Devil Festival in the museum... with official goods...
We'll be accepting orders for this week until Sunday, the 15th.
Hey, everyone...
I don't know... it hasn't changed a bit...
I think it's something like this... for the festival...
And now...
What's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong? Was it like this, like Metallica?
It was Metallica, yes... the book's "Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
As I explained to you...
There were hand towels...
There were hand towels, glow-in-the-dark things, wristbands...
Wristbands...
A bowl of kuutonken...
There is a collaboration set.
And more...
This time, there is a Mariko version.
I think I showed you this once.
This is how it looks like.
Please take a look.
The badge
and quotes
Trading
Clear
Clear card-like
We have some trading items, so please check them out.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
Is everything all right?
I'm still working on the living creature software, right, Flip?
I'm sure you all want this the most today.
This, huh?
Black Throat.
It's a high-end fish, a very high-end fish.
Well, this is what we're working on.
We'll give away our drawings on the day of the event, as we did last year.
And on the day of the event, as was the case last year, there will be a raffle at the entrance.
And if you win, they give you a present at random.
My parents won one before.
Whose was it?
My sister's.
Oh, I see...
They have a lot of clothes.
They're smiling. Clothes are coming.
So, and also, here's the latest news...
In the very first Festivo!
Ebinaka-chan and Nadechiko Takamine will be collaborating to do a BFF type thing!
Plans?
Scheduled.
Plans.
Plans are undecided, right?
Yes, because I suddenly said no on the day.
I don't want to play guitar anymore.
If that happened...
I'd just put the guitar down in front of you and retire.
Like an idol putting down the microphone.
Momoe Yamaguchi...
Putting the guitar down like this.
I don't know what I might say.
No, no, let me decide how I want to live.
Let me decide... no... maybe if the microphone goes crazy... the guitar would be nice...
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all at the Cannery Festival next February 23rd.
I hope you all will join us at the Cannery Festival next February 23rd.
So, that's about all I have to say. Is everything OK?
Do you have any news? Are you all right? Are you all right? Yes, I am.
You know, people in that industry, they love this.
You do this a lot, don't you?
There are many hand signs in the industry.
For example, this one.
Extend it.
I don't know, the conversation ended up being too short.
I mean, there's some kind of trouble over here.
Please keep the story a little longer.
It's a common thing in Xavier's Corner, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
You know what's the opposite of that? That's it... that's it... that's it... that's it... that's it... that's what Xavier's Corner is all about.
And you know what the opposite is?
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Right?
No, that's why they do this all the time.
Yes, that's right.
I don't think I've seen this one before.
Oh, yeah.
They don't do DREAM too often, do they?
Well, they don't like it.
Yeah.
Because I'm not a dragonfly.
No, no, no, no.
I'm giddy.
I'm not trying to catch you.
I'll do this one, Dream.
And I'll do this too.
And we'll do this too.
We're... we're... we're more old media than people say.
We're old media.
This kind of thing is still around.
That kind of thing...
What is this?
People nowadays don't understand why we cut with scissors.
I understand.
Why are you cutting this?
Cut?
For editing.
We used to use tape.
So it's really like now.
Editing...
Oh, shit.
I'm telling you, this is what I'm doing now, and this is what I'm doing behind the camera. - That's why I edited it, like this, and I really cut off this part that I didn't want, and I threw it out.
I cut this part here and this part there.
And then I put it up.
It's physical.
It's amazing.
But the point is, it's the same thing that we're doing now.
You know, the premiere, the final cut...
It's a strip of footage.
I cut here and here.
What we're doing is the same.
But that's what they're really doing in real life.
That's why this is happening.
That's why.
What is this? This?
This? This?
This?
What? What? This?
What? Which one?
In hand-sign terms, which one is it?
What? What? This one?
Xavier.
This has nothing to do with Xavier. This has nothing to do with Xavier.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- I'm sorry...
- Raiya, you wrote the words for me.
- You wrote it for me, Rakuya.
- The core of revolution
- And he wrote the kanji for this year's 2024.
We're announcing it tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
The 12th.
After tomorrow's announcement...
We'll do a live broadcast next week.
Something.
I think you said something about a million yen.
If it was true...
A million.
If you guessed right, it's a million.
A million. A million.
If I guessed it right, it's a million.
Isn't it a million yen?
A million.
A million dollars?
A million euros?
It's a million.
You're all stiff and won't put this part on.
The unit price part.
If I say yen, that's all I'll get.
A million.
A million what? Tomorrow!
- Wow! Oh, man, I'm so excited! - But I can tell you one thing, this is not it.
- But I can tell you one thing, this is definitely not it.
- What is it? - What is it?
- I don't know, this year.
- What's the symbolic word? - What's the symbolic word?
- What's the symbolic word?
What's the symbolic word for this year?
Sure, like 50-50.
It can be written in kanji, like "shina", "5"...
It's hard to understand.
Five.
Yes, I guess that's why.
Wow, so many different kinds of things.
A million bitcoins, that's a lot of money.
That's a lot of money.
Even that one bitcoin is worth a lot of money.
That's it then. Bitcoins.
Where are you going with this bitcoin? - I don't have to work anymore. I'll quit my job!
- Why don't you take the Bitcoin?
- Why don't you get some Bitcoins and quit? Let's all go to the hot springs together.
- I want to go!
- Let's rent out the whole place for a week or so.
- I'm going to thoroughly relax in this position at the hot springs.
- That would be great!
- We can watch Netflix.
- At the hot springs?
- That's the same thing we're doing!
- It's just a different place. - It's the same thing we do all the time.
Oh, well, well, well...
That's also why they're announcing next week's live broadcast.
So there's an announcement.
Next week. And we'll roll for an hour.
Rolling an hour, 7:00 p.m.
7:00 p.m.? No, no.
No, we're an hour early.
I hope to see you all there.
So I'll see you all next week.
Thank you.